Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Confess left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real?
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be
there and stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend!
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are
Rotten woman!
How dare you try to make a fool
of the great Captain Usopp!
Insulting me for having
the blood of a pirate?
Please, you don't have to do this, Usopp!
Klahadore?
Klahadore, are you there?
Hello, Klahadore?
No! Mary!
Mary!
What's going on?
What happened to you?
Please wake up! Mary!
Please don't die!
Oh, thank goodness.
You're still alive.
I was worried.
Mary!
You have to tell me who did this to you!
Klahadore! That's who!
He attacked me!
He's a...
he's a pirate!
He's never been anything else.
But how could that be?
He got close to you just so
he could steal your fortune.
That's all he ever wanted.
And what Usopp spoke about
yesterday was the truth.
That's right.
And that's what is most tragic.
When he learned the truth, he tried
his hardest to get us to hear him out.
But we were all too shallow-minded,
too confident in the
closed-off world we've
lived in for so long to
listen to a single word.
Quick! Run, Kaia!
They're gonna kill you!
I promise this will all
make sense tomorrow.
In our blind protection of
the villain in our midst,
we drove away the one brave
lad whose desperate resolve!
he enacted for the sake and safety
of every person of this village?
including you and I.
Someone help!
Mary needs help! No, miss.
It's of no use.
The entire staff is on leave.
No one has been here since yesterday.
What?
Then I just...
I'll find...
You cannot let yourself
get flustered, miss.
We know the attack has yet to begin,
so be calm and think clearly about
what it is you have to do next.
Because if Klahadore is the
thief we understand him to be,
and his goal is your fortune and your
mansion, then by all means let him have it.
None of this is worth
sacrificing your life over.
Yes.
It's a cruel truth, but you are the only
one who can stop Clawador now, Kaya.
Can you do it?
I know this is not your
burden, but still I must ask.
Yes, I understand, and I will do it.
This isn't a situation
I can run away from.
I know what consequences I face.
I will find Clawador
and I will finish this.
What?
You saw Clawador heading to the shore?
Yeah, and he had this weird,
scary look on his face.
Carrot, would you wake up?
Come on, it's way too early for this.
This is no time for laziness.
Horrible things could
be happening right now.
I still think the pirates
are going to attack soon.
I know our captain said that was a lie,
but I think he was the one that was lying.
Yeah, you're probably right.
It was weird.
He seemed off yesterday.
The captain wasn't his usual self.
It's Kaya.
She's all right.
Looks like something's
got her really bothered.
Yeah, walking around outside
by herself doesn't seem right.
Something's going on.
Something really weird.
Come forth, Meowban brothers!
Yes, Captain?
Did you call for us?
Well, did you?
Xiong! And Bucci!
Together we are the Meowban brothers!
At your service!
Bucci,
Xiong, we absolutely
must get up this hill,
but as you can plainly
see, our path is blocked.
What if he would be so kind as to
remove this obstacle immediately?
Hey! No way!
We couldn't do that!
He looks too strong!
Right, Bucci?
Oh, yeah, he's strong.
Way stronger than us.
Huh?
Besides, we just guard the
ship, not fight people!
He's got a point.
We're really not the guys
you want to send into battle.
So, they're a couple of pansies.
I guess they're not the
trump card after all.
Xiong, just do it already! Ah!
What? Please, not me! And hurry!
Okay, I'll go. Just stop yelling.
The guy's crying like a baby.
What are they doing down there?
Of all people, why force
that guy into a fight?
I'm gonna tear you off with these claws!
You just wait and see!
I'm a vicious killing machine,
and I'm coming for you!
You bad people!
You come any closer, and
I'll cut you in half!
I'm not joking!
I'll do it!
Not likely.
Impressed? Too bad.
It seems you fell for my little ruse.
I'm impressed you blocked me, considering
what a brilliant performance I gave.
Don't let the teeny bit
of skill you have cause
you to underestimate Siam
of the Meowpad Brothers.
Are you missing something?
Not that I would know anything about it.
There it is.
Cat burglar give me my swords back your
swords, but you already have a sword.
How greedy can you be?
Say goodbye swords.
Goodbye
Now I feel lighter
You really have to be faster,
because I'm agile as a cat.
Beach, you're up. Get in here.
She makes you up.
Faster, buddy!
Damn, Beach!
He got away from you!
Now he's right there, and
I'll hold him tight this time!
Careful, he's strong.
Stronger than I thought he'd
be, even without all his blades.
This is getting worse by the second.
If Tummy there would have landed on me,
I'd have been pounded into the dust.
We'll get him for sure this time!
You got that right!
One sword technique's not my
forte, fellas, but what the hell?
Let's go, Bootsie!
Right, Siam, let's do it!
Pussy with an old moth!
This isn't good!
They got him on the defensive!
What are you doing, Usam?
There's no way that
Zoro can gain any ground
if he's too busy blocking their attacks!
I'm gonna help him!
Take this!
Let's go!
This is our chance!
You're supposed to shoot
at the bad guys, you idiot!
But I did!
It was...
it was like he moved in
front of my shot on purpose!
But why would he do that?
You dumbass! Don't help me!
You want to die?
It's just a thought, but maybe it's
the two of us who just got saved.
If you had actually hit one of those guys,
they would have come after us instead.
Then we wouldn't have had a
chance of holding up against that.
What a guy.
All this time, he was worried about us.
If I just had one more sword,
I could take these guys.
I'm gonna get the swords.
If I can get them back to Zoro,
there'll be no way he can lose.
Let me get the swords.
Don't push yourself.
You can barely even stand up on your own.
Nubby!
Huuu!
Nami!
What do you need swords for?
No!
I'm sorry!
I can explain all of this!
The night has long since passed.
So why is it that you seem to have made
no progress on the plan? Captain! No!
He'll kill us all!
It's all over.
What the hell is going on?
To think that these
brats have held you back.
How the black cat pirates have fallen.
What have you got to say for yourself?
Jungle!
But, uh, well, I...
You said...
Sorry, sir, but you said letting the
kid go wouldn't cause any problems.
I did say that.
What's your point?
He's an idiot.
I knew no one would listen
to his warnings and he
would come stumbling back
to take a stand against us.
But the one thing I hadn't taken account
for was your inexcusable weakness.
We're not weak.
It's just that...
Who are you to call us weak?
What would you say, Captain Kuro?
You used to be quite the killer.
But face it, kuro, it's been three years!
and we haven't exactly
been living the good life?
waiting on a rich girl hand and foot.
Yeah, that's right.
For three long years, we've been out sinking
pirate ships and massacring villages.
Very good. Finished. No!
You've done nothing this whole time!
We've been killing you!
Butler, there's no way you
can beat the Mialban brothers!
Don't! Bucci! Xion! Stop!
YOU ARE NOT CAPTAIN ANYMORE!
So sorry, but we have to kill you!
What? He's behind him!
How the hell'd he...
I'm one of those crazy weapons.
Who are you going to kill?
He snuck out right behind us!
He's gone!
The Pussyfoot Maneuver!
You know, you're right.
I do feel a bit sluggish
after all these years.
He's handling them like
babies and those two
nearly defeated Zoro with
his pussyfoot maneuver.
Captain Kuro could shred everyone on this
beach before we drew our next breath.
We wouldn't even see it coming.
There is no escape from a
killing machine like him.
I knew he hadn't grown soft when
I saw that old habit of his.
That strange way of lifting his
glasses so that he won't cut his face.
It's like he never stopped
wearing those cat claws.
They're almost a part of his body.
Of course he hasn't
forgotten how to fight.
You're very lucky.
I'm feeling somewhat merciful.
Maybe these years on dry
land have made me soft.
I'll give you five minutes.
If you can't deal with the
situation here in five minutes
then I'll kill every last one of you.
Now have I made myself clear?
Oh, yes.
Yes, of course, that's perfectly clear.
Thank you for being so forgiving.
All we have to do is take
care of this one guy.
That's all.
Five minutes will be more
than enough time for them.
We nearly had him a few minutes ago.
We won't need one minute
to finish him this time.
We're counting on you.
Kill him, kill him dead.
What the?
Hey, easy there.
You can't just kick him.
Those are my swords.
How about a thanks?
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
You idiot!
It won't matter how many swords you have!
And now you'll die!
Only three of them!
Tiger!
You still don't get it.
The clock is ticking.
Carrying three swords won't help you at
all, unless you know three-sword style.
Oh no.
This is bad.
He took down the Meowbond
brothers with one attack!
Don't worry.
I can promise you everything will be
taken care of in less than five minutes.
Three.
Three minutes left.
I'll slaughter him.
Please, Captain.
I can do it.
Hypnotize me.
Just do it, captain!
He's still alive.
You do sloppy work.
So he is. I guess.
I'll let blubber protected his vitals?
Bucci, kill him!
What, really?
You back for more?
This guy knows business.
He was trouble when he was half this size.
Then jango had to flip his psycho switch.
Now's my chance!
I gotta wake that lazy jerk up.
While I still can?
What is that girl up to?
Something tricky, I'm sure.
Everyone else is busy
fighting for their lives!
And he's just sleeping.
Get up, you bum!
Nami, look out!
It was nice knowing you.
Duds it, quick!
Please, stop me!
I thought it was just a hypnotic
charm, but it's also his weapon.
Nami!
You cannot just go around
stepping on people's eyes!
How is that twerp still alive?
It's either the best timing or
the worst timing in the world.
I can't tell.
Uh, Luffy?
Luffy!
Crap, that guy's back in the battle.
No, this is terrible.
Five minutes will never be enough time.
That hurts, you jerk.
Why'd you do that?
Hey, sleeping beauty, that wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
You okay?
Nami, did you get hurt? Let me see it.
Oh, it's nothing. I'm fine.
I've done everything I can for now.
The rest is up to you.
Look, we have to win.
We can't afford to lose this fight.
Do you understand?
Okay, go.
Win this and protect my treasure.
Yeah, yeah, the treasure. I get it.
One minute and counting.
Karoo can't be serious.
We can't possibly finish
them in one minute.
Come on guys, stop messing
around and end this already
Bucci quickly there's
no more time to waste
Kill that three sword bastard.
I'll take care of the freaky bendable kid
I'm coming for you, Straw Hat!
Hey, wait!
Why is that shady butler here?
It's that kid.
Didn't he die falling off a cliff?
Nice trick.
Huh?
Don't ever sneak up on me.
Unless you want to die.
No, Usopp, are you okay?
Kaya, what are you doing here?
Oh, Lucy.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know how you'll ever forget me.
I just couldn't believe it.
That Klahadore is a
scheming, murdering pirate.
Never mind that.
Why are you here?
Kaya, your life is in danger.
I told you to run somewhere safe. I won't.
You're still here fighting.
I won't run.
You fought for me after
I treated you so badly.
Look at you, you're barely
alive, but you're still so brave!
I just...
This is no place for a lady.
Madam, please leave.
Please stop, don't do this.
Stop, stop this right now, claw at door!
I know what you're up to.
Mary already told me about everything.
What's the girl from the
mansion doing down here?
The whole reason that we're here
is to murder that little rich girl.
If she's here, then we don't
have to go to the village.
All we gotta do is kill her, right?
Clawador, please.
If you want my fortune, you can have it.
Take it all and leave
this village right now.
I'm begging you I will gladly
accept your fortune miss Kaya.
Thank you
But I want more you see simply
acquiring wealth isn't enough.
More than anything else!
What I want is peace.
You want peace?
Yes, just peace peace of mind.
It's simple really I I have
spent the last three years
earning the trust of the entire
village and to be honest,
I find this new sense of peace
and tranquility quite comforting.
When my plan comes to fruition, I will
live with this sublime peace of mind.
Yes.
The glorious comfort of a peaceful life.
Will be mine for forever and ever!
In short, these pirates are coming!
And you will leave your
fortune to me and die?
Miss Kaya, these things will happen.
No, you can't.
You just can't be.
Run away, Kaya.
There's no use talking to him.
Please, get out of here.
You're not Pahator.
No, you're not.
Kaya.
Leave here, right now. Never come back.
Yes, I see.
You're all grown up now.
So much has happened in
the last three years.
Miss Kaya.
Don't you remember the
things we went through?
We spent so much time together.
Even before your dear
sweet parents passed away.
You were more than my master.
You were my best friend.
So much time.
So many memories together we suffered
and together we rejoiced like family.
I took you on shopping trips to
the city I looked after you so
diligently when you were ill and we
used to talk for hours and hours.
Kaya listen to me I was devoted to you
for so long for so
very long I endured it.
I quietly suffered so
that today I could end
your life and take
everything that I deserve.
I who was once the feared
and respected Captain Kuro,
had to bow and humble myself
before some snot-nosed little girl.
It went against every fiber of my being.
Damn you!
Can you understand the depth
of these daily insults?
Can you understand the rage created by
those transgressions against my pride?
Thank you for reminding me.
Usopp, I owe you for
hitting me. Let's get even.
Oh no, Usopp!
If I recall, you hit me as
hard as you could, right?
Oh
He hates getting hit that much he's
about to have a really bad day!
As a kid,
I never stopped Searching
for a great treasure I had
a map in my mind That I
knew would lead me I had to
find my way to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land was in my
grasp And I wouldn't let go
La, la, la,
la My only dream La, la,
la, la, la I won't stop
chasing it until it comes true!
But if the world ever
changes I call out your name
We can return to the time
when everything's the same!
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade Waiting
for that one true dream?